const words = [
    {question: 'halò', answer: 'hello'},
    {question: 'mar sin leat', answer: 'goodbye'},
    {question: 'balach', answer: 'boy'},
    {question: 'nighean', answer: 'girl'},
    {question: 'uaine', answer: 'green'},
    {question: 'gorm', answer: 'blue'},
    {question: 'sona', answer: 'happy'},
    {question: 'brònach', answer: 'sad'},
    {question: 'mòr', answer: 'big'},
    {question: 'beag', answer: 'small'}
]

module.exports = { words }
